export let resolve = [
    {
        question: '"Elementary, my dear ......"',
        answer: () => ['watson']
    },
    {
        question: '"To infinity and ......"',
        answer: () => ['beyond']
    },
    {
        question: `Who said "I'm gonna make him an offer he can't refuse"?`,
        answer: () => ['godfather', 'don carleone', "marlon brando"]
    },
    {
        question: `"Toto, I've a feeling we're not in ...... anymore."`,
        answer: () => ['kansas']
    },
    {
        question: '"A census taker once tried to test me. I ate his liver with some fava beans and a nice ......."',
        answer: () => ['chianti']
    },
    {
        question: '"Red right ...."',
        answer: () => ['hand']
    },
    {
        question: 'Hannah + Mikkel',
        answer: () => ['jonas', 'adam', 'jonas kahnwald']
    },
    {
        question: 'aHR0cHM6Ly9kcml2ZS5nb29nbGUuY29tL2ZpbGU<wbr>vZC8xSlhhR2xmX2l3QTZMS084aGlENngtV<wbr>VdqNmVPX053V3kvdmlldz91c3A9c2hhcmluZw==',
        answer: () => ['mag']
    },
    {
        question: 'aHR0cHM6Ly9kcml2ZS5nb29nbGUuY29tL2ZpbGUv<wbr>ZC8xQVJtZmpyRzhudFpfV3VadEp3UndxR2p0cEdyQV<wbr>NzOEYvdmlldz91c3A9c2hhcmluZw==',
        answer: () => ['34558914442']
    },
    {
        question: 'Find the white rabbit in html',
        answer: () => [localStorage.getItem('white_rabbit')]
    }
]